南京论坛那是
希望之声在
今年的10月份好专门是针对2020年的大选所举办的一系列的活动我们希望从
非常一些深度的探讨那来
来大家来了解这个2020年的大选那么今天我们非常荣幸的是邀请到了
两位顶级的东西方的学者
从历史的角度来谈谈
今年大选的意义以及川普总统连任的一面
好那这个节目呢现在是在这个天亮时分这个频道上播出哈
那么哪里买一个频道是叫而是新田在他的频道叫做走入美国这两个频道我们在这里也要
谢谢这个天亮先生啊
那么对张天亮了加大了文在介绍一下哪有的观众会说你说什么我们就是
章天亮的粉丝毫不像减少了
我们都知道好像天亮先生的是纽约飞天大学的教授
同时也是历史文化学者自己能又是时事评论家但是呢其实官员章天亮先生
其他的事情呢我觉得大家未必都知道得很
很清楚华
其实我想在下半场呢
关于这个张贴亮教授那我再多做一些补助
创也许大家会觉得我老是这样吗
好的那我们接下来那就欢迎我们另外一的一位嘉宾啊
汉生教授
Professor Victor Hansen
A Professor Hansen Welcome to the event
Freeman
Times
我叫tears in Chinese and just have to
Transmit RSS What do we say about you
OK
那么
汉森教授拿他是著名的斯坦福大学胡佛研究所的资深研究员军事历史
史学家和经典学
宜家
怎么教经典学家家呢对他其实用通俗的话来讲那他就是研究
西方文明的语言文学和哲学等等方面以及美国立国的
我的根源
那么汉生教授他是全美国最高产
俺的作家之一他已经写了20多不输了那么而且他的所写的这些时事评论文章
在美国几百家的
这个媒体
想看灯
他曾教授了他也是在多所大学教书除了在斯坦福大学而且还在比赛
比方说在中西部所有非常偏远的
你去教书是他对美国的民情
非常的了解
最独特的一点是什么呢
郑教授虽然他已经是非常的有名是被认为全美最重要的学者只要
但是他几十年来都坚持在加州中谷的农场
卡农
在晶莹在他家传
四大的农场
这一点的就可以看出他并不是一个在象牙塔
塔里的学者
醉了这也就是让他能够成为唯一的在2016年大选的时候他几乎可以说是唯一
唯一的准确的就是认为川普
会当选的
保守派学者
他之后就写了一本书叫
Case for Trump
从这里有他这本说的case创
那么这本书呢
是在纽约时报的最畅销书的排行榜上是呆了至少五周
也获得了川普总统的推荐
那么
其实每天我都有十几二十几家的媒体像汉生教授邀约那么我们今天所以说
你是非常的荣幸啊希望之声的也是非常荣幸的成为
汉森教授接受采访的唯一的一个中文的
今天已经是从三年多前就开始啊
采访他说今天的机会非常难
大家了解今天两位中西方的这个顶尖学者的观点画从历史的钟声
所以呢大家留意一下如果说您这方面有问题的话那你抓住机会好像我们的这个右边的这个留言
我们也许会在结束之后看成较差一点是
时间的话那我们会请
请他来回答一下您的问题所以这也是抓住这个机会
但张的量比较少能会多待一些时间后因为还是要时间比较忙他就会在前面的半个小时的样子
但是我们有张天亮教授在后面做详细的一个价
好的那么很快说一下今天的安排我们基本上会是两个主要的话题那每一个话题那声叫
要说都会
做一个他的一个演讲然后那只方为社会做一个非常简精简的
翻译啊
然后天亮博士来会更好
教授做一个
这种对话
最最后我们希望有点时间可以
回答大家的问题
OK好首先呢我就想
我们这个话题就是怎么样从这个历史的重生和角度来看
今年的总统
统大选
Superposition of elastic
淘宝的first topic is on
From the
Storage
Angle
Under the desk
How do you see
These years
Independent
What grade do you feel over
The dominant media are the posters
Establishment
Uniprot
设备不会用2000cc
Black mirror
Means
Return to tell the sexy.com protranslating telegram
Even though the proton win2016
Reminders
That is going to win
Metamorfosi Institute for the transcript
Truffle
Devicemotion covid的Paul variable having the receiver
Santa Maria novella
绥中
Beautiful
Trump Tower
Which people who
External energy Balance Industry
Contractors
Compensation
Ground policy
Communist party
Incredible stories
物流分拨
We can Express urdu
Satisfaction MS
Driver for input source
509 the mail service
VS taxable
Jordan
Apple Watch This in perspective
Curio mechanism
Prudential very hard life the gender bias
Hello Resident receive the democratic
Binary
Memories
The new frontier of America for oral sex
Attacking across the universe electron-packager undergraduate
What control the democratic party so that investors
Vicroads westerners
Joe biden
而这样的
Institutionalized disbursements
Whenever wherever senas
Pepper Camp and Because of
Rebalance
Reception and religion or 360 procalcitonin demonstrating
I will your virtual Canada
Mr.sandman fastcompany.com understatement
Very comsol
Self-service
Replsetreconfig Vampire food was recovered
或者
World Cup football
Then Maybe he can carry the stranger Cross the finish LINE
OK我非常简单的说一下话
那么还是要说他就说那2016年我们都看到这个媒体也好啊或者是
这些搞明掉了他们都搞错了话
那么能2020年的他们在此人认为他们可能会赢但是在2016年的像这个的马克思Institute
这叫民主民族学院的话
如果干个拉拉斯姆森若干个认识教程来再也不能叫另外一名调吧就是就是不是这些主
主流媒体的民调
他们都已经是叫出来这个全不会赢
但是呢他们那么这一次来大家都觉得还是很奇怪啊就是川普的发言者为什么在民调中没有
没有出声音
今年那就是很多的怎么暴乱了很多的这个打架强之类的话
那再加上这些病毒吧装也是非常特别的事情
虽然他说简单说他刚才就是假的
他说这个拜登已经不是一个民主党的一个中间派了他不代表美民主党的主流民意他这个科
何子豪
他的时代这就是民主党里头的极左派的诸多的这些个这些个东西啊
这些对新政啊等等之类的
他对民主党的
主流他就其实现在是没有什么吸引力的
拜登那77岁躲在家里的这个地下室里头呆了七个月啊
用现在呢他大大了若干个月吧那么现在就是看他最后有没有就冲过觉得大打足球是吧没事做
足球14场
如果能撑得住的话他大概最后能把请把球赛打完吧
Superfast Hansen gender
Open the History of United States Why do How do you think the significance
Of the selection of is that
Mathematical economics 1036
Whether the United States
Frm
荣耀3C
NBA
Never return status 405 method not agree on an entity
This is very important because
Fluctuation
The Welcome no longer
Discovery
索尼公司
我没烧的barrier
Nationalism
We will be careful
We will deliver capital Transformers
那种karrimor DJ
This.setstate
San fran
Alteration
Durex
Vnp83
和那个request is coming of Internet with money with incomplete
玻璃钢格板
有什么
Back
Universal power supply chains On my god
I don't know about the vagaries of education parenteral
This is what the color by email template
Evaluation Center Facebook
Twitter
Asymmetrical
Latest News Now
Printable
Santander Bank
Funerale
Another one is 2048
Fortran padding
Experimental
Word you have little more about one will
Giorgetti marbles the cake with name
Spec2000
Calgary
Nobody can see More
Balwant
Mhz Conference on availability
Because covid-19 606
Suppliers
Thalmic
Change in the suspension service representative
Recombinant everyone for the Chinese government
Latitude is no longer
Welcome
Will help aspires
We are preserved in world and reflected make sure never happen again
Which all Bill maher not to work with console
What my company conservative gilbert
Nexus 6
M200 website
China
Sensible
American power supply Unit
Vikatan imbalances in our current work and Beyond programmable because It is more power
我们不一致
Content-aware projection for
Elisa the result is very similar
OK
好很很简单翻译下划
约翰森教授说那把这时间倒退回1860年那时候是南北战争的前夕华林可能因为自营
行了40%的票但他赢下了美国总统
自那次选举行英文是非常非常关键的
另外一个很关键的选举是1940年的时候美国面临要不要介入第2次世界大战的时间和他们那手术还
装逼
别入了好不管怎么说我们都知道那两次选举的
结果
现在美国的左派的基本上是一个叫什么来着就是什么都不伪装了画以前还会还会显得忠利亚
呀你媒体向各媒体这个这个
民主党的主流向各主流啊他现在都不会装了什么都不管了反正就是印上了好吧我现在就把瑞克
大法官的听证什么都不管了这应该上了
所以呢包括说这个辩论也好啊等等之类的话这个脸书啊
封杀一边的声音不合格不理另外一点的声音
都不管不准不管中立这硬上了这是反映出他们的某种信心
还在教室也说起来想起来中国大陆的政府中共中共政府的
我的也是这样的
把那么大个那个病毒给放出来那么祸害全球
他那绝对不用道歉不用道歉就这么着了这就应上他说这个那就是
这个全球性的这个做派吧
和这个美国的左派都有相
相就是相似之处
Your presence of elasticity factors on any
到时候他们出来给他听
天亮博士
Good afternoon everyone and Professor handsome is honored to be with you
YouTube
Fractional graph with What You said
The steak is too high
Is not about higher or lower tax
Neither is it about your router
It's about the wealth life
It isn't a logical what
Freedom
Slavery
Is about whether the United States will become a totally terrorism
Or not
Moreover I think
Because a Stable and prosperous America is the
Cornerstone of the World
If
The United States sales
The whole world feels
Sonar
Situational
Trump is fighting
Two worlds
Sometime
118b
Understand Chinese
Comic party
I want to
Exercise
PDF the Chinese company of ecology
Ccp
Is not equal to China
Ccp is small and organized crime book
我要Chinese people
Expressed
Under is rule
Web
Insist
习近平is promoting the community of
Shared future of
Mankind
Fortunately
His community is the communist
Community
Which would be a disaster for humanity
手机上trumpet
Vim svm
Observed
People's Republic of
那Windows
Distorted
Criminal Deals with
Ccp from What has been reported by the New York post about his
披散着白的
Berthold technologies
Trump is fighting
Waste
搜索里怎么
United States
Almost every minute
Immediate这个site
Except for Fox News reports in diffuse orders
Happy combo Balance
家里点
The media Industry has abandoned everything in principle of journalism
Mbk companies
Twitter Facebook Google assistant
Chorus
所谓consider in the password
Still doing everything within their scope of authority
News
Incorrect padding family
SOS occasions location
我来
Will be living
Saturn and life test
Control of our country
So I called and ideological work
Communism
Like a Because I recalled and logical because companies May take Over the United States
走1364
Flight
秋
The Zoo do Christian values on Which the United States
我帮你
So I want to make clear that
Comments
A simple idea
Smt godsend
Antivirus
Procurement
Factors
Last minute
Be very careful about
Dmitri places in Chinese
Give me probably one minute
所以我觉得现在美国大选的
是川普现在打两场
战争这不是说一个税高还是说的或者是说这个
社会秩序能不能够维系的问题
现在的问题的话实际上就是说
美国面临的是自由还是奴役
川普现在把布朗战争的话一场
他是跟这个中共之间的战争当然中共是不等于中国的
但是就是如果拜登当选的
华文重现在就是纽约邮报说
发表的这个
这个消息的话我们已经看到了就是
这个
如果拜登当选的话
他能中共识也有很多黑幕的交易吗他会成为中共的一个体现的没往这样的话美国等于就被中共给空
控制了这是川普必须迎战争赢得战争的第1点
第2点的话就穿不在达的第2场
就是在美国国内的这些社会主义
主义者或者说极左分子
几乎所有现在美国的这些主流的媒体所谓的主要媒体
除了像发朋友作者是牛肉头砸向纽约邮报或者是
福克斯新闻
或者还有一些其他别的
你的稍微小一点的但是其他比
别的话都变成了就是
10周白等的一个拉拉队长
就是所有现在我们看到的这个组的主流媒体所谓的主流媒体的话就不多
放弃了
所有的这个
做一个新闻工作者的一个底线包括那个大的科技公司向推着下Facebook向那个Google
他们都在这个帮助
这个
拜登
所以说就是说如果我们看到他们现在的这种表演包括他们对这种
我现在的封锁的话我们就知道如果大东营
我们将来美国会生活在这个共产主义的那种
就是这个对这种这种社会秩序之下
所以呢我想
我想把这个东西的话成为意识形态的战争这就是这次大选
其实不是一场选举而是一场新意识形态的战争我们必须要赢
否则的话就说整个美国的这个建国的基石就会动摇
而且他最后想说的是就是共产党它并不是一个
简单单的一种思想它其实那是反神而且是反人类的按照马克思的说法的话它就是一
是一个鞋领
手test
过来happy
我要
American People don't put
Careful to distinguish
This shop
Communist
Tory government
The data flow in Chinese
A strategy for the Chinese people
Because my first
Numbers african American support
Is very high
University for the Hong Kong protesters二号f x
Samples were used
What time is for the government is very hard
China with Secret
Communist party
Centerpoint
American culture and politics in stages of Chinese counterparts
We are for International students
American perfecting press
Caliburn someone connected the Chinese
Maybe one person 645 cutler after
Agent
Chinese government
喂
Reconstituted study group
Capital One credit card penetration China
Orbital
Commercial
The First Bank China service
猫
你是谁
Imperialist
Coreos
E-commerce forests
Mesos chronos Imperial VS m4v
Was burning the projecting about American
People because resonates
Wood of Al
Very dangerous because
China's New hybrid
Popular culture
Much better understanding of American caregivers
Much better understand English corpus boyfriends conduit
Magic
Transamerica foundations of media
Entertainment
The utility of Liverpool University the dissemination of bacillus licheniformis movies
Based on the test
Chinese government was the best Wireless connectors
7-eleven
怎么成为sirius black
Amber
It is very hard for the US government to both of these letters powershell
Window.scroll Believe in government and replace the Chinese people in pakistan
Would you have always
What is my family or Hollywood charges of Brown James
What president of Harvard University tuition
No no no
Me
手表处responsibilities
Underworld because
IPhone
The first time my wife
Will try to come from China and I will be finished China
Lc filter
We will go back to becoming more be going back to work on a contest
广德世家都是国王VS
From the Chinese
Recast
Not authorized to be reciprocated and I think of happiness
Will be important to try something new and stupid was the best movie Now on
Taiwan
The fireworks
Playboy
Industrial independent
Very very carefully work at Taiwan self Korea Japan
Australian scene in the world in a student Can I want to take the economy and in this country for Bank
Reelportal Chinese communist party
ITS ability to spend happen
Analysis Justin
When you have an element
我会去
出来出来吧
Because of Trump was to be seen by China
Prisoners reputation of interior
Resistance
Replacement
Physical Memory or common table
Interactive monitor the standard
China
Swan River is acceptable region viewstate
Underwater basic vendor
Refinement
好的那还真叫什么呢说了挺多的话我就非常简单的去概括一下首先他说美国的人民好对于这
这个对于这个台湾那香港是非常支持
是的他们能够认得清这个
中共和他所欺压的中国民众的区别
但是他说的这个中共学美国哈比美国文学中国要要厉害的多话
Renaissance 35万的这个中国留学生10%到20那是和中共有关系的10%呢
那几乎是几千人就是间谍
是这个
只是专门的间谍
最让他们在美国国内发起对这个
川普总统的各种攻击吧就说这个川普总统是帝国主义殖民主义压孔外主义啊
这些话好多能进行美国国内左派的共鸣
那么他就说那中共对这个美国的了解方方面面的了解远远超过当初苏共
对美国的了解
最终共其实是蛮厉害的
那么他说那是事所以现在呢其实美国面临非常非常
这是来自于中共的非常可怕的威胁
那他也说了如果他这次选举
这个拜登影的话那将是一场
很大的灾难
因为中共会变得更加感大他会认为说美国的这个做法吧而就是这是川普这个做法他是
不行的那么你美国就是美国人民拒绝的这个做法
最多中共就会更加的胆大那么真无论是针对台湾还是包括针对澳大利亚那么所有这些根
现在川普这个政府
姐姐猛地把他们都会抢
就是强烈的就是来
搜索来欺负吧
来做这个事情
最大的梅拜登是完全没有这方面的能力包括智力或者经历
取得抗中共的
他非常担心的地方
The professor Hansen talking about the previous audience
会生疑他们应把握手
I just think you know the dirty talk about How important this is
Usually in the US presidential election the foreign policy
泡b1b的decision factors
Efficient
Do you think how do you think this is between the relation between US and China
Referring to what you just ate
Do you think
The US popular public
Know about that No what's in stock
And the soldiers
Translator
Chinese
刚才谈到这个
这个
中共的跟美国的关系在这次大选中如何的重要那就不知道汉生教授
说怎么想在这一次
是的大选中美国的民众选民他们了不了解这样的一个情况立刻
Thirty minutes
So perfect
What is given for this reason you like to foreign policy is not used
你先去
也许我的actionbar
Iplaysoft
This report 2016 Blank
Karabiner
Generic
更坏的
Wsk
Stranger
Production workshop
不是这个意思
US people in the world
New technologies you want kill saudi arabia United arab emirates not reported
Livermorium C8
You wanna go back into the women Do you want to give more money to give any government
Do you accept the wheel on the ukrainian circuit shown a former soviet University
Sanctions against North Korea
Do you want to stop
Call China to tell
We have no answers
Vol05
Vue Promise covid-19 approach to increase size limit covid-19
University new and our computadora do we
Confine
你是我
Green and they don't know what to get into
Because
Pages that Trump is wrong on
Lessons and everybody human brain
We have no alternative
Reputable Stupid man
Open WeChat
Cardboard is an terraform power
我没写对
It is very good
Insert figure below the American restaurant in
Crossfit
Category company in music methodologies and sample
Validates resource
Inhibit the mechanisms
Resident aerosols
China is very dangerous
What is beginning to the office 2007 We have to come from Chinese imperialism
Material
有什么效果
阿妹
Israel ablestik
Father bipartisan 414ce
Establishment 15ml
What is an even web.config privacy
The web service
Queen Elizabeth l
Chinese human
America really Beautiful In every written about microscopic
Cortana
你说的Mac numbers of amorphous billgates-li excitable Financial stocks
China
Silence weather for entrepreneurs
Chapter2
Airchina
Cross-border electronic signature
We got the Journal of Us president of personality of people coming out
International University press the weather will get what you do in Hong Kong
Will just What happen to believe the WeChat
这个是written to the Chinese people will practice The boy in Taiwan
不用WiFi on Trump not connected with the incumbent avcapturemoviefileoutput
Mms
Man and Iron fist
People talking about
Android be Silent Night
Babel-polyfill successful
OK
他是文鸟很简单的跟大家来报告一下
的那他就说现在反对川普的人是因反对而反对话他就是支持反对
第2的你如果看具体做的事情
清华一件件川普做的事情包括外交事务你都会他们都不反对话结果非常好
所以呢他们不看结果只看这个这个就这个过程
第3个拿他是2016年那个川普已经明确的反对中共了那时候两党的外交外交人人士
是把都一致的攻击川普华
那么第4呢他说即使是自由派和左派
私下里他们可能同意全部做的
色情
但是呢他们表面上就
他他还是表妹上还是反对
他们当然也一直要是维护这个人权吗维护人权也是这个民主党一个一个纲领
但是呢
只说不练
只说不练好啥也不做因为这里头诸多的公司里
等等之类的现在呢川普已经领着美国去反对中共的话他们也跳上战车在香港
问题上阿哥各种要问题上他也发声谴责
随着某种意义上的他们反对的川普
我其实打造了一个平台
让他们现在反而变得更加强大他们就是左派画
间左派也借着这个川普开的
开始正式投吧你去批评中共从中得到得到好
这也正是他的这么一个看法
The pressure sensor is very limited
Practices of Status for few minutes
So I would like to get to the question
Professor You did you do to write a letter of work
Decay锁床
Search for two thousand sixteen lektion so for this year
Would you think of
The case for Trump
我要提问
Really clover normally because his 253 provincial
Where distinguish them from
W public and establishment
Secure
Borders and legal matters and illegal immigration reindustrialization the Core of United States
Beatles
Income in China Japan
Deregulation economy
Encouraging
Calcineurin
Open to sell
Mfcclub.com
We are the strongest
College entrance
Malik
Which group or study gdpr
Microphone women
Because these issues have been recognized as an invention or
November
我的边
Delivery was going to be one what
Sally was going to do with a directory
Yukirin abroad
原来Q我
Undergraduate American people I think there
Mlb election
Voilin21 preston
Extend the lifting percent of American elaborate
Castlevania
We don't know what you thinking
Arizona breakwaters
NVIDIA
Websphinx
等一下
Use current location
Emerson
I can take to my account letter writing I can Take your time
I can't agree that night can spend in walking on my home
I can take a custom field in inspector
Adjust
I can take orders
Disunity
Impossible not just want to go there may be performed by Nobel way
Decided
California San Jose
Enough is enough
Archiver
IPad VS
Intertemporal approximate the drivers to be defeated by targeting the most wonderful world
Destroy economy
River Island
Standoff China will continue
Lm secretary of A person in 60
Grand prix
Am very very very very very very very important than electoral College
A360 close
Redmine set charset
Strengthen State
Paris
李undecidable turn from the Pennsylvania North Carolina or higher Education in the venue
What's the weather outside
不要说
Make up your mind
One very early Bird American 19a的
Anyone else begin public order was about a Point from reckoned with previous
郭玲的高坡
Recommend an analyst points
就不要300
Will draw pictures
Utc-12
Portable way to percentage of wireless network coverage
Android voice was about 300644 election
Animals portable 2000rmb lena
The Wall Street
Undecided recanati
Metallica-one will be ordered 2063
How to interpret official
November
而holding the most people that never enough is enough
Alexander Wang
Am I now my breakfast
Sambal
Do not take away all our building
Stop
Overwatch
识别错误差不多
好那么基本上新田问题就说那2016年你校准了到底谁赢了
就川普能赢
2020年你觉得呢你你怎么说呢
好那太正教授就说了
大汉森教授就说那他是首先就是川普奔来应该是大屏
你输赢的因为他五件事情全做对了话
其中包括数把这个边境边境把他的收藏了关起来那么区分好这个
玉米非法移民和合法移民
他重新加强了美国的核心的制造业
那么对中共那是非常严厉那么也把经济弄得很好减税减归那么经济这个能源工业的
等等之类的吧建成了美国最强的经济
那么所有她说的那个都都说到做到了
所以呢那这些民众相信他们也都也都也都认同化也都认同
但他说现在的问题是什么画
10%的15%的美国人他们既不说又又不又他们还没有做决
他还没有做决定他们可能怎么反应
到最终了他们一定会做决定
他们决定有两个可能性可能会做哈
一个决定的就是说他们现在实在是受不了了被一群关了这么久话
就是咱们问我不想过这样的日子来这是这个兑换上拜登能够不过这个日子就行
把他们这个怎么把川普换下去
这是一种可能的结果好第2个呢就是说这么多的暴乱这么多的这个这个这个问题华纳美
美国要继续往前走支持川普
把这些东西都解决
那么是他另外一个决定
这些人那这个中间派他们会怎么倒
不知道
但是呢他们一定会做出去
决定的
所以那那如果一旦做出决定的话它会形成一个广泛的一个效果好是整个的准备摇摆
在珠宝或者是中西部和中部中东部
河南部他们其实选民都差不多的想法都差不多
这一辆一旦这个这个人群啊在最后的时间做做出决定来的话呢
整个都会出现一个清晰的结果
他也说了话以前的去了好多莉在今天卡特是大幅领先这个罗纳德里根
那么罗丹你就说零天八个点啊就会罗曼罗纳德里根是10% 10个点应过来
那么也包括说希拉里也是上次是银九个点在这个民调和民调研究各点的最后是输掉了选举
等等之类的吧他说所有这些事情吧就是看最后的一段时
Professor Hansen University road people concerned about the world in Mobile email
CBS sports and Play out What do you think
World ranking
Don't have a strong
Bipartisan governance
City California New York University
American
Which
Ivi.ru
Are you well
Hotels
Legislators my California New York
我要
Chamber
Amundsen-scott setinterval bills with China congressional research into Cloud native
Wise
Widespread
What about privacy
News
Oxford College of physicians situations
Corruption And scalable we would not important actionable because
Arabic
Confined my president
Feature extraction
On Trump is not whenever He was not find variable Declaration
What's the weather of canberra
Used Cars
Industry
Maintaining of our house
美光的presentation for everyone works
Booking.com x7000
Android res
Michigan Wisconsin Minnesota
Self-help
Republican governors of democratic legislatures legislators
Vondom products max2
Institut republican
Trident
Vicky and selection is to water resistant affecting percent of度
The Final Singapore sales
Conservative anisotropy field
Style burhan Tumblr
Little people who feel
American Express
Friends with them after identifier
MS
Big tap
Install for video surveillance mechanism service eucalyptus
Today
Ask me who is performed by text fields
Favor
Syria Trump will be better mind
Westfield toiletries
Babel-polyfill
Is much water
User
Not reply
Arthropoda divided by
Word
Triplet question like what you think is going to rain
Do you think you better and then you were four years ago
And some ways of questions favourite Trump and where the sexual
Uniform
装备
Monster ball to another question movie
好吧更好artery
YouTube
Lyricist albatron morellino win2000 360
The representative
Beautiful person
And appreciated the manager
Liverpool Chinatown
Wayne State election
魔女service delivery
Unilever 2017
Units Wednesday to record anything to beginning
Everyday
Continue after recovery from the buyers
The boy scandal
End of a good to be expensive to go to bed in exercising
Is your favorite girl
好的那非常简单的说就说他刚才说的是邮寄选票华新田关心就是邮寄选票多大程度和影响
想选举那简单的说那教授就说呢
在那种宏州把子对铁兰州的民主党的州呢
他们搞特别假假东西因为一党独大麻民之党独大
他们虽然在那可以弄到很多选票最后会把那些影响那些州的众议院的议席
可能会导致这个民主党会会保住中院
但是难影响不了参远影响不了总统
因为这个美国国富所设计的选举人团的制度化等影响不了那些
另外呢就是关于这个这个害羞的川普或者害羞的川普的选民那么现在科技已经非常非常
我想发达的话你随便回答一个问题是我支持川普的不好这个高科技公司全都不可以把你这个信息抓取
有谁都可以把你研究点头号
绝他说很多一个不敢说他就不说宁可不说我投票那个时候再说
最能包括说你作为这个民调的话你得绕着问你才能问出真相了你不能直接问你投川普还是
头戴灯
你再绕着问才能问出真相来
所以那些方便把它就觉得就是这是看吧我想他的想法就是
如果说
现在还有几天时间好美三天那就川普的可能就说
他现在已经这个事情他的这个感染过去了话
没几天民警就会变化没几天明天就会变化如果一直保持这种正向的变化的话他说川普很可能会议
亚洲要等kubernetes Professor and Just The Last words of honesty
电脑CPU and Professor Dr John
Q
Nice to meet you professor
Thank you for further
Thank you
好的非常感谢啊还升教授我想我们的听证会有如果就是资方为自己做
做了非常坚毅精要的很精彩的一些
翻译好但是呢我们接下来的时间那我们就会用中文来讲然后是
麦克风的也是主要交给张天亮教授
天亮不是你觉得刚才对于
丁教授讲的这些呢总体来说你有什么
想要分享的
我觉得很遗憾他下去了
是我有一些话想咯
跟他讲
因为就是他刚才提到就10%到10%
15的这个选民的话那就是还没有决定投票给谁
但是实际上就是我们现在看到的红左派的最终反应来说的话那天凉好象很深
拿thinkers
好好请继续
Calibre
OK所以说就是他说10%的15%的前面还没有决定但是就是我们看到现在左派的他这
这些就是做的一些切割好就
就是耍了一些小伎俩其实那就是他们知道这个做
准备决定的选民说是为决定但是其实他们很有可能
会投给川普这里面有三个
证据好的一个证据的话那就是
刚才还生教授也提到了就是你现在的这个生活情
情况比10年前好还是坏
那么根据这个民调的话那56%的人认为他们的生活比
过去4年就四年之前要好
这说明就是他们在川普的
我的这个政策下了他们是已经受
手艺了
最后我觉得他们没有理由不同川普的票
就是不管你是不是已经是就是这个决定了但是我觉得就是这个比例的话大概是56%的人的话他
他们生活都应该比之前过得更好
更何况就说在这种异形影响的情况下就是这个他们
还能够就是感觉的
以前过得好那就说明就是川普之前给他们就是
带来的这些比如说简说呀就这种这种这种就是
放松一些不一定啊等等就是对他来说的话是非常有好处的
现在美国第3季度的GDP的话还没有公布
如果公布的话呢据说是
大概会有34%的反弹
因为GDP的第3季度跟第2季度相比的会增加24%
教你三分之一的鸭子这就是一个微型的反弹
这个的话对于川普来说的话是非常非常有力的这也说明就是说在川普的这个政府就下了这个1行
其实对经济的影响并不大包括现在看到股市
都已经就是基本上回到了至二月份的这个
这个情况
这个我觉得是一个对川普比较有利的这个这个数据号
怎么还有一个数据的就说
在这个
就是
就是关于这个就是这个人对这个落差包括就是在那个难
边的木边境建墙那就这些事情就是一般人是怎么反应的
因为我觉得裸露的话题
其实是川普在选举过程中的话它应该反复强调的一点
也就是说
现在有三分之二的人称为
他们
就是喜欢落落的
那么你就如果你喜欢乱*的话你就会知道在民主党的那些州的话对于这个
就是这些抢劫纵火犯
那样的一种放纵民主党地址
这些是长和是周长的
话其实对于
选民来说的话是无法容忍的今天我们刚刚看到不是新闻的一条消息
说就是在这个Portland
就是在这个华盛顿的这个华人顿州的这个波特兰
由于这个波特兰市长的不作为就造成
这个波特兰
很多很多人他们现在在导向共和党现在共和党出来挑战用州的华盛顿其实是一个身兰州
但是现在的话就是
就是这个这个这个华盛顿州的话那就是在他在某些地方的话我觉得某些选区的话他都不会议员他的事
市长的话都有可能会翻红
现在在那个波特兰附近有一个就是民主党和共和党人他才29岁一个年轻人挑战现在
带着这个民主党的市长好像
那现在就他好像是能够募集到的款要
要比那个市场要多很多
所以我觉得就是如果2/3的美国人
喜欢这个法律和秩序的话那么这些人的话他们也可能会投川普
然后再有一个的话就是我们看到就是在
就是
选民的这种热情啊就是我觉得对于川普的热情非常的高涨
今天我在我
我自己的频道下看到一个消息就是Hotel
这个周能有一个
就是这个有一个有一个那个州的居民吗叫的频道下留言他如果排队排了两个小时
终于把
选票委托
投下去了
因为我的话它是一个传统的这种就是摇摆州行共和党必须要赢得这个周的话才能够赢得大选
他就是个害我的话就是昨天我看到的消息就是大概有百分之
大概有20万张券
选票了已经头
投下去了
如果你要是按照这个投票的时间算好就从你开放这个投票站到
投票的这个数化就是这么多天以来俄亥俄州的投票率的话比过去高了三倍
就是过去的话大概就到这个时候
就开放投票账号比如说过了三天大概只有6万张选票投下去那个我还有的话现在已经投了20个20万张选票
而且都是排的打对巨头
我觉得就是说一般来说倾向于共和党的人的话他们愿意亲身去投票所以我觉得就是从排队投票的那个
热情上来说的话
也应该是共和党占上风
刚才我觉得先前的一个非常好的问题就是其实我也是想着汉森教授讲的但是没有机会
就是
你们大家都提到就是这个蜂蜜泡的水好
就是这个这个
对外政策外交关系政策的话他本来不应该是一个大选中非常重要的一个议题
或者是说这个决定选民投票意向的一个议题
但是现在的话呢
其实我觉得川普他应该做的事
就是我刚才在第1段就是
这个刚才用用英文讲的那段
川普应该把这个国际事务跟国内事物联系起来就是说他要讲清楚我们现在这个这场
投票的话其实是一场意识形态的战争
不管是在
这个国国外对于中国共产党的这个战争是对共产主义的这个战争
还在国内对于社会主义
这些这些机构的战争其实社会主义他们只是
共产主义的一个
就是美妆也而以一个变种而已
如果
川普应该当选明明确的说如果你们要是想
支持社会主义或者支持共产主义的话你们看一看香港人
他们遇到的事
在我们这么强烈的知识
下的话那么香港现在还就是说被中共剥夺的自由然后就是这个包括他们的选举都推出了一年
如果共产党胜利的话
如果美国失败的话
会变成一个共产党国家的话那么
实际上美国人民她的生活状态就跟现在中国大陆的生活状态
还是要跟那些在维吾尔在那个在这个西藏在心将被镇压的那些人是一样的
我觉得川普应该
Make The case
就是跟那个美国老百姓讲清楚
我看到就是在
这一次好就是这个第3次这个总统辩论他们又选了一个
极端支持民主党的
你的这个这个这个这个moderator就是这个辩论的这个
主持人这个主持人的话他是
整个一个家族
十几年的历史大量的给民主党捐款包括在2012年他们过年的时候他们直接到白宫中的奥巴马也会
不过这个嵌入这个圣诞节和新年
所以你可以看到就是这样的一个人被选为一个总统辩论的主持人带领本来是
舞蹈patent important他应该是他应该是这个不偏不倚的但是他们选择这样的一个组织
他所有选择的一体都是对川普不利的一提
几乎上几乎都是比如像可爱美亲什么就是什么什么环境啊
就是这个这个就是把环境变化天气变化
然后的话呢这个
还有就是像可为难听呀什么之类的
这些东西在以前都反复提出来过了为什么第3次还要听
第1次比第2次提第3次还要提就是因为想办法给川普难看我觉得川普在辩论的时候一定不能够录入
他们的圈套中
川普一定要讲清楚如果拜登当选的话会对美国国家安全造成危险
川普一定要讲
大灯
整个家族
大陆犯罪
然后的话把这个事情跟美国的老百姓讲清楚如果你们愿意
是一个跟中共合作的这样的一个一个一个犯罪家族
就是一个像像像这个
我不用特别难听的词了这样的一个人来管理美国的话
那么美国是非常非常危险的
如果拜登把我们所有现在就是川普政府的这个政策
全都给
取消掉的话其实因为拜登上老是说他要quebec
好的policy
就川普定的那些不管是家属也好国际关系也好他都要误会
那么就是旧都要都要退回去
那么
中国的话
就真的是就是美国的话就真会被中国做所数控制川普的话就是他们其中的一个体现没我就支持在
现在川普第3次
总统辩论的时候一定要讲清楚的一个问题
好听的不是那其实我们现在也有很多的听众观众朋友在提问那首先我
我想也是在这里真的感谢
我们的听众观众朋友的支持包括张杰希David苏
秀玲徐留影儿正在暂住这个天亮时分的频道非常感谢
这是
感谢就会这些听众观众朋友
那么
天地不是有听众就是问号就说
像这个我们看到过有些过去几天这个拜登和他儿子的这些事情就是
为什么不启动
调查和起
另外就是说这个
新闻媒体互相社交媒体跟他们之间的这种关系要好像
非常的密切这个
到底是为什么你们家
哦这个为什么还没有起
起初因为我觉得联邦调查局里面一定是有这个
就是深层政府的话一定是有一个的State
这就是为什么你会看到就是及时帮这个这个这个当时的这个威名称的那个店主吧
这个计算机交给FBI去年年底的时候聚焦改变到现在整整九个月的时间
就sbr没有任何反应
最奇巧的
一个是就是
当川普因为这个跟我喊那个新上任的那个总统泽民死的通话的时候在一起
2019年7月25号通话的时候
整整国会骚扰到他
半年的时期
一直到2月份
就不要弹劾他
而FBI这个时候手动明明是有一个这么强有力的证据
本来他们是可以一个delegate串
就是他们可以就是给川普脱罪犯他们把这东西藏起来他们不拿出来
这里面现在的问题就变得非常的严重所以我觉得即使是这个
就是如果真的要起诉的话这个司法不必须要采取
做事必须要尽快的才说是首先我觉得就是现在国会在
就是傻*呢
怎么说就发传票给这个FBI吗就是这个联邦调查局
要求他们说明
到底这
这个令牌你们拿到之后那他是干什么来了
是吧那么我觉得就是现在美国的司法部
司法部如果要行动的话是吗不必须要赶紧行的斯拉夫现在我觉得应该他们跟住院你联系
能够现在公布的那那邮件的话上半个邮件的话我觉得应该尽快工作是现在我觉得还有一些
这个考拉bullet
没事那就是能够咯
祝愿你的那个邮件相配合的那些东西比如说那个原来
这个
500等手下有一个叫做库里的人这个人的话她因为金融欺诈入狱了吗
然后他在2019年被释放的时候他把他的那个Gmail看
这个密码交出来然后的话就是你们那个里边的话还有很多拜登的那些黑幕这些黑幕的话他是可以
可以和
祝愿你手里边的这些这些email的话是可以
互相印证的
所以我觉得就是这些方面的东西呀就是应该赶快的就是这个公布出来让美国人民看
现在左派的画在拼命的就是在在拍的危险
他们的女儿一条就是在拼命的推销他们的那个就是叙事
他们就说包括那个adams
他花了三年的事
就是那个congressman就是那个house里面那个Intelligence
肯尼迪好就是国际国国会的情报委员会的这个主席
他花了三年的时间一直在讲说这个川普
跟俄罗斯超模瓦什么之类的我有证券什么之类的你会发现他已经发了三年的话
他什么证据都没有最后发现从不缺什么什么事都没有
就在这样的情况
他今天又出来发慌出了川普这个东西
你是来自于这个俄罗斯
所以我觉得不管来自于来自于谁
只有把非常过硬的证据呈现在老百姓的面前到时候你看一看就是美国的老百姓会怎么讲
我觉得这个
这个可能才是
当我们有了这个
美国道歉怎么讲就是他们当他们发出声音的时候会被这个FBI也会形成压力强大的舆论压力
其实当年的水门事件就是因为那个王行政post的那个那个的思路的说法就是那还得有报那个深*
不断的揭露就是这个你就说话这个干干的什么干的什么
形成了一个强大的压力
我觉得现在
必须要把这个证据的话庆会的释放出来让美国民众形成这种民意的压力然后让司法部去调查那个
那个那个那个FBI调查这个这个很特别的
那还有观众在问哦那如果川普总统他没有
当初没有发动跟中共中共的这个贸易站的话会不会这一切就不会这样子发生
生川普是不是在为他自己的任性
买单怎么
跟这个一点关系都没有我觉得唯一的理由就是说他们之所以
就是
一直在攻击川普因为川普他是一个来自于华盛顿枣子币以外的人
而这个长期以来就是在这个
美国的官僚系统华就在美国的事务官这这群人里面就是具体办事的
这些人的话他们跟那些原来的就是这个就是被选举的向那个奥巴马时代也好或者是克林顿时代
小布什时代一号这些政府官的话他们已经形成了一个利益共同体
结果现在的话突然间上来了一个川普
川普的话作为一个被选举的总统的话他跟
现在
整个这个是无关这个关掉系统的话他是没有关系的他也没有利益
太没有什么把柄抓在他们的手
所以川普的话他可以把刀阔斧的
去整顿这个华盛顿当然就这些
已经在这个沼泽里面去
就是这个滚得一身泥巴然后就是已经是这个
就是满身的这种污泥和这个就是罪行的这些人的话他们当然会觉得
非常的害怕
这个我觉得是一个原因
更大的一个原因
的话我就觉得因为川普的话他是
这个就是
回归常识回归美国的这种国父们建国的价值
而这个东西的话跟整个这个建制派
在全面左转
这个方向的话是完全相反的
所以他们反扑了其实并不是因为是川普
今天如果不是川普话的彭斯
换了本卡死了会员换了Michael
Mike pompeo他们会做的事情是一模一样的一个非常典型的例子就是
Univariate里根总统是一个如此幽默是吧
充满了个人魅力的这样的一个人可是当年那些左派们对他的攻击的话也是非常疯狂
到那时他们还顾及脸面没有像现在这么风光现在就是已经是完全把他们的
这些里面都是就是这个这个伪装都已经撕下去了
好的那段时间就是很快好那我们差不多一个小时要收尾的话我想在收尾的时候我想讲一下我们今天这个美华
把金论坛那个题目叫
中西方的顶尖学者来剖析美国大选的历史
那我们都知道汉森教授刚才介绍了还是还是几
其实叫西方经典历史
睡觉那么那么天亮博士呢其实是我可以叫做这个东方和东方的经典历史
使学者把那天亮
不是说别叫他学家叫他学者
其实我啊这个我采访天亮天朗不是才能很多年了啊我其实我的本质是一个媒体工作者金
今天是我的政治工作啊
在我的天朗不是比较了解我在我在这里
你那给大家介绍一下
这是那么整天我是那是
电计算机工程或者台湾的电脑工程吧
计算机工程博士现在是中文系的教授
不仅他是历史文化学者不仅是
时政评论家他通山是专栏作家
那么也是多个这个电视电台的这个出席的这样一个嘉宾
同时你是大型相似节目笑谈风云的话把中国20 20 44
重新讲一遍啊大型
节目小台风云的住家人
他同时那也是小说家
这是剧作家
再想想看一个一个叫做功课背景
现在做中文系主任本的
本身你很惊人了啊
这一天我是确实是学会
大学跨中西好那么那么坚通这个
精通古今
横向纵向都是我觉得非常的优秀
我觉得我们今天本来就是气
请讲请她和韩森博士同台吧我觉得真的是最最佳的学者呈现给我们的
观众朋友
那么今天时间用他实在不够好我们希望以后还有更多的一个机会话然后这个天亮博士和这个潘森教授
能够有更多的对话给我们带来这个
关于美国问题和这个历史问题的一个深刻的一个看法
所以能让另外那天亮博士现在又做的一个系列节目叫中华文明史话
中华人民
他的曲子那个那个这个角度啊和这个叫谭峰又不一样
那么节目呢每周都在出那么在这个人希望之城的话
向市场的网站里头
你看得到
好的是我给大家做一个补充啊我们今天的这个主题
这个
这怎么讲呢
那就是最重要的像一个分量和的角度
所以范围也是算式为
体量不是解密不知道观众朋友你刚才
你的介绍对对对如果敢动你觉得刚才对方为揭秘这个天亮博士
是你觉得有什么感受如果
觉得哎呀真的是太好了请您在下面留言啊
另外乐队今天得这样的一种形式确实是我们的第1次尝试
我们真的觉得非常的荣幸能够请到天安博士
这样的一个顶尖的
这个中华的文化历史的学者加上这个美国的降雨为西方文明的
经典学家汉森教授一起同台呢
给我听个朋友来做一个非常不同的一个深度的分析和分享
让您觉得这样的形式和内容怎么样
也希望的观众朋友能够在下面留言也让我们知道您的看法
也便于我们以后今后再决定
是不是继续做这样的一些常识
和探讨
另外呢假如您觉得对于汉生教授所讲的内容
很有兴趣的话我在这里那也给自己做一个广告
那因为我是就是规律性的会采访还生教授刚刚有就推出一个两
2级的系列
就是韩教授专门来讲
美国的学校好
对于
西方文明历史的教育到底出了什么问题跟现在的事是美国人社会
会得这种分裂
有什么样的关系那如果你感兴趣的话就可以到新田的走入美国的频道去观看
你说的叫我觉得那个张贴膜是其实关于这个话题也做过非常深入的钻专题的节目好就可能又是一个很
好一个同台这个
有机会加上我再来安排吧好不好看呀
好棉体谢谢非常感谢感谢天亮博士我们这块宝地然后
然后他也非常感谢我们的
观众朋友后来又有那个Lily王也是在赞助这个频道非常感谢我们的观众会好今天的
节目就到这里了我们下周六啊还是有这个